MBULELO PANI

• Web Developer •

ABOUT ME

I am a junior web developer, based in Cape Town. I have experience in building, testing and maintaining full stack websites. I also have experience working alone as well as working within a team, and I love to learn on the go. My passion is designing the functionality of neat and interactive websites.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Full name - Mbulelo Pani

Sex - Male

Date of birth - 29/08/1997

Region - Cape Town, Western Cape

Nationality - South African

Email - Mbulelopani09@gmail.com

Phone - 073 703 6422

Profile link - mbulelopani.herokuapp.com

EXPERIENCE

Apr 2021 - present - TouchFoundry

Web Developer Intern

- Frontend development
- Testing, debugging
- Code cleanup

Dec 2020 - Apr 2021 - LC Studio

Web Developer Intern

- Backend development
- Code testing and cleanup
- Frontend testing

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2019 - Jan 2020 - Sage Futuremakers Foundation

Volunteer facilitator (part time)

- Assist facilitator in tutoring programming to youngsters
- Plan lessons
- \bullet Assist in recruiting potential students from the

townships

Jan 2020 (3 weeks) - Old Mutual

Job Shadowing

• Shadowed project manager, robotics developers

_

SKILLS

Frontend design	Frameworks	Soft skills
HTML	NodeJS	Teamwork
CSS	React,VueJS	Learning
Javascript	NodeJS	Accountability
Boostrap 4	MongoDB	Open-mindedness
Python	MySQL	Critical thinking
Mobile responsiveness	Git	Time management

EDUCATION

Feb- Aug, 2020 • Lifechoices Academy

- Course: Fullstack Web Development, Lifeskills

June - Nov, 2019 • Melisizwe Computer Lab Project

- Course: Introduction to Programming, Python, Advanced Python

- National Certificate : Systems Development

EDUCATION

2016 - Dec, 2018 • Northlink College

- Course: Logical Systems, Electrical Engineering

- Certificate: N4

2011 - 2015 • Sizimisele Technical High School

- Course : Electrical Engineering - Certificate : Matric

ACTIVITIES

Interests

Database design Machine learning Software design Physics

Hobbies

Web design Reading Gaming Meditation Circuit building

Volunteering

Organization: Harare CAN
Foundation Duration: Aug - Dec,

Tasks: deliver food parcels to poverty stricken areas around

Harare, Khayelitsha.

REFERENCES

Khanya Qongqo

NGO: Harare CAN Foundation
Position: Marketer/manager
Contact: Qongqokhanya@gmail.com

Gift Khangamwa

NGO: SageFuturemakersFoundation

Position: Facilitator **Contact:** Gift@melisizwe.co.za